<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Grace Nolan</title>
    <description>Student from New Zealand</description>
    <link>http://gracenolan.me</link>
    <atom:link href="http://gracenolan.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Introductions</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello! My name is Grace and I (currently) live in New Zealand. I am studying computer science at University of Waikato.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a bunch of things that I would like to blog about. I will make a short list in a moment. Something that I have been thinking about during the creation of this blog is what I am going to talk about and who my target audience will be. I have various projects that I am working on. Right now, I am trying to decide if I am going to focus on the backlogs, or start afresh from today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or I could compromise. If I am having a bit of quiet time, I can blog about past projects. I will put the date of when I was working on that project so the projects show up in correct order…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My writing style is more like a diary than formal, how-to articles. I hope that by adding this personal touch, my posts will be more interesting for you as well as me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s that list of things that I promised. It is of the things I am thinking of writing about:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The creation of the Computer Science Student Society at Waikato Uni&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learning Android for location aware music application (and working with shitty research software) &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Anita Borg retreat in Sydney and a reflection on being a women in tech&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Planning the upcoming Computer Science outreach programme at University of Waikato&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Working remotely over the summer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CommTECH camp in Indonesia&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learning flask, data science and making information meaningful&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Working on a helpdesk and interesting things that happen when doing tech support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are reading this blog and there is something from this list you would like to read sooner rather than later, feel free to leave a comment or &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#103;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#099;&amp;#101;&amp;#046;&amp;#109;&amp;#046;&amp;#110;&amp;#111;&amp;#108;&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&quot;&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>http://gracenolan.me/Introductions/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://gracenolan.me/Introductions/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>